<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Foot orthotics on Cryos Technologies | Technology products for podiatrists</title>
    <link>http://www.cryos.com/en/categories/foot-orthotics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Foot orthotics on Cryos Technologies | Technology products for podiatrists</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 21:19:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.cryos.com/en/categories/foot-orthotics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Steps To Wearing Foot Orthotics - Cryos Technologies</title>
      <link>http://www.cryos.com/en/steps-to-wearing-foot-orthotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 21:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.cryos.com/en/steps-to-wearing-foot-orthotics/</guid>
      <description>The wearing of foot orthotics is a prescribed treatment that remedies foot and postural problems. However, before obtaining an orthotic prescription, a certified health professional must be consulted to diagnose and determine the nature of the problem. Read further to discover the main steps you need to take to get a foot orthotic prescription from a Doctor of Podiatric Medicine (DPM), your foot and postural health specialist.
WHAT ARE THE REASONS THAT LEAD TO A FIRST CONSULTATION FOR FOOT ORTHOTICS?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postural Evaluation By Imaging - Cryos Technologies</title>
      <link>http://www.cryos.com/en/postural-evaluation-by-imaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.cryos.com/en/postural-evaluation-by-imaging/</guid>
      <description>Health professionals use imaging devices and systems for a variety of medical purposes. A validated and recommended approach used by some foot doctors is to use imaging systems to more accurately evaluate and measure postural and biomechanical problems. The visual nature of this technology allows patients to more easily understand the mechanics behind their condition and its impact on their posture.
WHAT IS POSTURAL IMAGING? Postural imaging is a measurement tool that helps with the diagnostic process by providing objective data in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2D/3D Foot Morphology- Cryos Technologies</title>
      <link>http://www.cryos.com/en/2d-3d-analysis-foot-morphology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.cryos.com/en/2d-3d-analysis-foot-morphology/</guid>
      <description>Custom-made orthotics are created by taking impressions of the feet. Precision is of the utmost importance in achieving the intended results of the treatment. While there are several impression taking techniques, some have been proven to be more effective and increase the quality of orthotic devices. Read on to get a foot specialists opinion on 2D and 3D impression taking techniques
WHY DOES A DPM TAKE FOOTPRINTS? Following the diagnosis, the DPM will prescribe the treatment necessary to correct the problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foot Orthotics and Surgery - Cryos Technologies</title>
      <link>http://www.cryos.com/en/the-benefits-of-foot-orthotics-before-and-after-surgery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.cryos.com/en/the-benefits-of-foot-orthotics-before-and-after-surgery/</guid>
      <description>Forefoot surgery is a treatment used for conditions such as hallux abducto valgus (a deformity commonly called a bunion). When a patient is experiencing pain or limitations that are detrimental to his or her quality of life, surgery in the forefoot is a possible solution. In fact, surgical treatment may be combined with foot orthotics to attain increased beneficial effects that can be felt both before and after surgery.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>