<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Foot orthotics on Cryos</title>
    <link>http://systems-analyst-elephant-50207.netlify.com/en/categories/foot-orthotics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Foot orthotics on Cryos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 21:19:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://systems-analyst-elephant-50207.netlify.com/en/categories/foot-orthotics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Steps To Wearing Foot Orthotics - Cryos Technologies</title>
      <link>http://systems-analyst-elephant-50207.netlify.com/en/steps-to-wearing-foot-orthotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 21:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://systems-analyst-elephant-50207.netlify.com/en/steps-to-wearing-foot-orthotics/</guid>
      <description>The wearing of foot orthotics is a prescribed treatment that remedies foot and postural problems. However, before obtaining an orthotic prescription, a certified health professional must be consulted to diagnose and determine the nature of the problem. Read further to discover the main steps you need to take to get a foot orthotic prescription from a Doctor of Podiatric Medicine (DPM), your foot and postural health specialist.
WHAT ARE THE REASONS THAT LEAD TO A FIRST CONSULTATION FOR FOOT ORTHOTICS?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postural Evaluation By Imaging - Cryos Technologies</title>
      <link>http://systems-analyst-elephant-50207.netlify.com/en/postural-evaluation-by-imaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://systems-analyst-elephant-50207.netlify.com/en/postural-evaluation-by-imaging/</guid>
      <description>Health professionals use imaging devices and systems for a variety of medical purposes. A validated and recommended approach used by some foot doctors is to use imaging systems to more accurately evaluate and measure postural and biomechanical problems. The visual nature of this technology allows patients to more easily understand the mechanics behind their condition and its impact on their posture.
WHAT IS POSTURAL IMAGING? Postural imaging is a measurement tool that helps with the diagnostic process by providing objective data in real time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>